{
  "level": "Primary",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is a computer?",
      "options": ["Television", "Radio", "Electronic machine", "Fan"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of the computer is used to type?",
      "options": ["Mouse", "Keyboard", "Monitor", "Speaker"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which device is used to click?",
      "options": ["Keyboard", "Printer", "Mouse", "Scanner"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is an output device?",
      "options": ["Mouse", "Keyboard", "Monitor", "CPU"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which key is used to leave space while typing?",
      "options": ["Enter", "Shift", "Spacebar", "Caps Lock"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a mouse help us do?",
      "options": ["Type letters", "Move the pointer", "Print paper", "Hear sound"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is used to hear sound?",
      "options": ["Monitor", "Speaker", "Keyboard", "CPU"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part shows what we type?",
      "options": ["CPU", "Mouse", "Monitor", "Printer"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is used to print on paper?",
      "options": ["Scanner", "Printer", "Speaker", "Mouse"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one is a computer machine?",
      "options": ["Radio", "Fan", "Laptop", "Bulb"],
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]
}
